question_data =[
{
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Sports",
    "question": "Roger Federer is a famous soccer player.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
    ]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
"question": "In &quot;Undertale&quot;, the main character of the game is Sans.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"category": "Entertainment: Television",
"question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klingons are commonly referred to as &quot;Black Elves&quot;.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
"question": "The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "Science &amp; Nature",
"question": "A plant that has a life cycle for more than a year is known as an annual.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"category": "Entertainment: Television",
"question": "Klingons once had a period of Democracy in their history, they referred to it as the &quot;Dark Times&quot;.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"category": "Entertainment: Music",
"question": "The Beatles&#039; band name was inspired by the band The Crickets.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "hard",
"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
"question": "The first &quot;Metal Gear&quot; game was released for the PlayStation 1.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
"question": "The song &quot;Megalovania&quot; by Toby Fox made its third appearence in the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot;.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "Entertainment: Music",
"question": "The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
}
]
